Guide to the Cartoon art collection, 1926-1988.
Cartoon art collection
- Series I. Cartoon Art, Prints, and Releases
  - Subseries Im. Mutt and Jeff by Al Smith
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, January-March, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      65 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, April-June, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      58 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      1 piece of original Sunday strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      21 pieces of original Sunday strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      44 pieces of original Sunday strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      37 original Sunday strips, one strip missing glued on additions.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      5 original Sunday strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      1 original Sunday strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      13 original Sunday strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff colored copies, February-August, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Mutt and Jeff blue, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Mutt and Jeff coloring diagrams, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Mutt and Jeff coloring diagrams, January-October, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Mutt and Jeff long strips (copies), 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Mutt and Jeff long strips (copies), 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 2-4)
    - Negatives for Sunday Strips, ca. 1978-1981 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
    - Negatives for Sunday Strips, ca. 1978-1981 (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
    - Negatives for Sunday Strips, ca. 1978-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
  - Subseries In. Red Ryder by Fred Harman
    - Copyrights, 1948-1951 (Box 53, Folder 1-3)
    - Sunday and daily copyrights, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
    - Red Ryder daily releases, 1949-1950, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 6-7)
    - Red Ryder daily releases, 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 8-11)
    - Red Ryder Sunday releases, 1938-1950, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 12-13)
    - Red Ryder Sunday releases, 1958-1964 (Box 54, Folder 1-5)
    - Sunday color tear sheets, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Red Ryder promo1948, 19 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Subseries Io. Sal A. Mander by Chris Gassett
    - Sal A. Mander original drawings, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      29 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Sal A. Mander original drawings, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      72 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Sal A. Mander releases (Box 65, Folder 51)
  - Subseries Io. Sparky Watts by Boody Rogers
    - Sparky Watts originals (Box 32, Folder 1)
      5 original drawings. Original drawings of Sparky Watts by Boody Rogers, 5 pages of what may either be an issue of Sparky Watts or a segment of Sparky Watts in Big Shot Comics. There is no date, but it was found in a box of proofs from the mid-1940s. These pages are not in any of the proofs of Big Shot Comics or Sparky Watts included in the box of proofs.
    - Sparky Watts issue 3 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Subseries Iq. Stoker by Henry Boltinoff
    - Stoker originals, July-December, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      93 original drawings.
    - Stoker original drawings, January-June, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      118 original drawings.
    - Stoker original drawings, July-December, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      130 original drawings.
    - Stoker original drawings, January-April, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      86 original drawings.
    - Stoker original drawings, May-September, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      92 original drawings.
  - Subseries Ir. This Funny World by various artists, alphabetically
    - Ackerman, Bruce, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Alexander, Florence (Box 9, Folder 2)
      3 original drawings.
    - Anderson, Clair, ca. 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      2 original drawings. Subjects include hippies.
    - Arno, Ed, ca. 1967-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      36 original drawings.
    - Arno, Ed, ca. 1967-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      14 original drawings, oversized.
    - Baginski, Frank, ca. 1967-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      43 original drawings. Subjects include, police/law, hunting, fencing, librarians, psychiatrists, boxing, office.
    - Bardulf, Ueland, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      2 original drawings, oversized.
    - Bartalos, Mike, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      1 original drawings. Subjects include fishing.
    - Barth, Larry, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      12 original drawings. Subjects include doctors, mountain climbing, hunting.
    - Battaglia, Robert, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      7 original drawings.
    - Biscardi, Dominick A., 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      4 original drawings.
    - Blanchard, M., ca. 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      30 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors, law, sports, scouts, hippies.
    - Bloodworth, Alvin H., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      1 original drawings.
    - Boltinoff, Henry, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      78 original drawings, oversized.
    - Brown, Bo, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      31 original drawings. Subjects include baseball, tennis.
    - Busino, Orlando, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      90 original drawings.
    - Busino, Orlando, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      101 original drawings.
    - Busino, Orlando, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      127 original drawings.
    - Busino, Orlando, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Cantone, Vic, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      1 original drawing, oversized. Subject includes fishing.
    - Cassady Cartoons, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      8 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include football.
    - Cochran, Bruce, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      5 original drawings. Subjects include football, hippies.
    - Cochran, Bruce, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      6 original drawings, oversized.
    - Cole, Artemas, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Dahlin, Ed, ca.1967 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      5 original drawings. Subjects include doctors, hunting, fishing, Christmas, skiing.
    - Dahlin, Ed, ca.1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      22 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors, hunting, fishing, Christmas, skiing.
    - Davey, Bill, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      9 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include Bicentennial, boxing, fishing.
    - Dawes, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Dawley, J. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      1 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include ballet.
    - de Angelo, Tom (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Delgado, Roy, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      1 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors.
    - Dole, George, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      7 original drawings. Subjects include doctors, business.
    - Dole, George, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      4 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors, business.
    - Dunkel, Courtney, ca. 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      4 original drawings, oversized.
    - Eaton, Don C., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Engleman, Earl W., ca. 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      37 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include Christmas.
    - Escourido, J. (name illegible), ca. 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      2 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include hippies, animals.
    - Estes, James, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      2 original drawings. Subjects include art museum.
    - Farris, Joseph G., ca. 1969-1976 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      6 original drawings. Subjects include tennis, aliens, mountain climbing, psychiatrists, golf, animals, business.
    - Farris, Joseph G., ca. 1969-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      15 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include tennis, aliens, mountain climbing, psychiatrists, golf, animals, business.
    - Filchock, Martin, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Franchioni, Arnoldo, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      12 original dawings, signed "Francho". Subjects include animals.
    - Franchioni, Arnoldo, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      2 original drawings, signed "Francho", oversized. Subjects include animals.
    - Gallagher, John, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      52 original drawings, oversized.
    - Garel, Leo, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      58 original drawings, oversized.
    - Gately, George, ca. 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      25 original drawings, oversized. Artist of "Heathcliff" strip; see separate worksheet. Subjects include boxing, doctors.
    - Getsler, Sylvia, ca. 1967-1975 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      53original drawings, oversized.
    - Gilligan, Clarence M. (Box 9, Folder 26)
      1 original drawing.
    - Giuffre, Martin, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      4 original drawings. Subjects include fishing, bowling, baseball, golf.
    - Giuffre, Martin, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      5 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include fishing, bowling, baseball, golf.
    - Graham, Ed, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      6 original drawings. Subjects include trains, horse racing, business, politics.
    - Graham, Ed, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      10 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include trains, horse racing, business, politics.
    - Green, Gerald H., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Green, Herb, ca. 1969 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      5 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors.
    - Grosart, Don (Box 9, Folder 29)
      6 original drawings. Subjects include fishing, doctors.
    - Habbick, Andrew S., ca. 1968-1977 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      9 original drawings.
    - Habbick, Andrew S., ca. 1968-1977 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      105 original drawings, oversized.
    - Hageman, Robert M., ca. 1967-1979 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      99 original drawings.
    - Hageman, Robert M., ca. 1967-1979 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      19 original drawings, oversized.
    - Hancock, Malcolm, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      3 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include animals.
    - Harris, E. A., 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      3 original drawings. Subjects include Noah's ark.
    - Harris, Larry, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      3 original drawings. Subjects include doctors.
    - Harris, Sidney, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      3 original drawings. Subjects include business.
    - Henderson III, Charles W., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Herman, Leonard, ca. 1967-1976 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      21 original drawings.
    - Herman, Leonard, ca. 1967-1976 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      69 original drawings, oversized.
    - Herman, Leonard, ca. 1967-1976 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      57 original drawings, oversized.
    - Hider, Reginald, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      4 pieces of original cartoon art, signed "Reg Hider". From Rochester, NY. Subjects include fishing, mountain climbing.
    - Hirsch, Dave, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      1 piece of original cartoon art
    - Hoest, William P., ca. 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      69 original drawings.
    - Hoest, William P., ca. 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      68 original drawings.
    - Hoest, William P., ca. 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      40 original drawings.
    - Hoest, William P., ca. 1967-1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      83 original drawings, oversized.
    - Hoifjeld, Norman, ca. 1970 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      6 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors, business.
    - Huffine, Dave, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      22 original drawings. Subjects include baseball, Christmas.
    - Huffine, Dave, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      8 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include baseball, Christmas.
    - Isler, Alfred W., ca. 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      3 original drawings. Subjects include fencing, water skiing.
    - James, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      2 original drawings. Subjects include martial arts.
    - Johns, Al (Box 10, Folder 4)
      1 original drawings. Subjects include martial arts.
    - Katz, Brian, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      3 original drawings. Subjects include business, psychiatrists.
    - +, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      9 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include business, psychiatrists.
    - Kaufman, Al, ca. 1967-1977 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Kearney, John (Box 10, Folder 6)
      2 original drawings. Subjects include hunting.
    - Keller, Reamer, ca. 1971-1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      44 original drawings.
    - Keller, Reamer, ca. 1971-1979 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      60 original drawings, oversized.
    - Key, Ted, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Keziah, Fred, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      1 original drawing. Subjects include psychiatrists.
    - Koru, Ibrahim Cihan, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      1 piece of original cartoon art, signed 'Cihan". Subjects include Noah's ark.
    - Lepper, Edwin, ca. 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      11 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include lawyers.
    - Linkert, Lo, ca. 1969-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      18 original drawings. Subjects include baseball, police, business, hippies, doctors.
    - Lucas, Dick, ca. 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      27 original drawings. Subjects include baseball, business, skiing, doctors, Christmas, psychiatrists, factory workers.
    - Lucky, Fred, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Lundberg, Gustav (Box 74, Folder 4)
      10 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include police.
    - Malone, Don (Box 74, Folder 5)
      2 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include animals.
    - Marcus, Jerry, ca. 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      20 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include prison, law, doctors, business.
    - Markow, Jack, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      12 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include baseball, figure skating.
    - Matthews, Doris (Box 10, Folder 14)
      7 original drawings. Subjects include animals, business.
    - McCormick, Bob, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      1 original drawing, oversized.
    - McCourt, A. A., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Messinger, Marc, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      1 original drawing, oversized, signed "Marco".
    - Michaud, Roland (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Monahan, Jeffrey J., ca. 1970-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      112 original drawings.
    - Monahan, Jeffrey J., ca. 1970-1979 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      21 original drawings, oversized.
    - Morin, Ray, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      5 original drawings. Subjects include doctors, gardening, law, animals.
    - Morin, Ray, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      4 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors, gardening, law, animals.
    - Morrie (Box 10, Folder 19)
      1 original drawing. Subjects include animals.
    - Myers, Eugene M., 1967 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      3original drawings.
    - Myers, Eugene M., 1967 - 1978 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Myers, V. Gene, 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      21 original drawings. Subjects include animals, firefighters, fishing, horse racing.
    - Myers, V. Gene, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Nitka, ca. 1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      6 original drawings.
    - O'Malley, Bill (Box 10, Folder 23)
      1 original drawing. Subjects include baseball.
    - Orehek, Donald A., ca. 1967-1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      60 original drawings.
    - Orehek, Donald A., ca. 1967-1979 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      55 original drawings, oversized.
    - Piane, Al, ca. 1969-1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      21 original drawings. Subjects include golf.
    - Piane, Al, ca. 1969-1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      15 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include golf.
    - Porges, Paul Peter (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Pottier, Art, ca. 1967 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      7 original drawings. Subjects include doctors, golf, business, astronauts, law, birdwatching, hunting.
    - Pottier, Art, ca. 1967 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      7 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include doctors, golf, business, astronauts, law, birdwatching, hunting.
    - Rich, Gloria L., 1972 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      1 original drawing, oversized, also signed by "Mark Shap".
    - Roberge, Frank (Box 10, Folder 28)
      1 original drawing. Subjects include doctors.
    - Sabo, Joseph, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      10 original drawings. Subjects include fishing, hunting, swimming.
    - Schochet, Bob, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      94 original drawings.
    - Schochet, Bob, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Sematones, Frank, ca. 1970 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Serrano (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Sherman, Goddard, ca. 1972-1979 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Shirvanian, Vahan, ca. 1967-1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      14 original drawings. Subjects include animals, fishing.
    - Shirvanian, Vahan, ca. 1967-1977 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      16 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include animals, fishing.
    - Skiles, Charles (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Sprague, Andrew, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      3 original drawings, unsigned, name on the back of one, lettering similar on other two.
    - Stamaty, Stanley (Box 75, Folder 14)
      1 original drawing, oversized. Subjects include boy scouts.
    - Stein, Eli (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Surace, Fred, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      27 original drawings. Subjects include baseball, tennis, boxing, hunting, fishing.
    - Surace, Fred, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      7 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include baseball, tennis, boxing, hunting, fishing.
    - Thompson, Ben (Box 10, Folder 39)
      2 original drawing.
    - Vanselow, W. A., 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      20 original drawings. Subjects include hunting, golf.
    - Various, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      Black and white line cuts by various artists. These are not originals but are paste-ups of cartoons to be printed.
    - Verdura, John, 1971-1972, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      2 original drawings. More elaborately drawn than many of the other cartoons. Subjects include fishing, police, Ancient Egypt.
    - Verdura, John, 1971-1972, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      11 original drawings, oversized. More elaborately drawn than many of the other cartoons. Subjects include fishing, police, Ancient Egypt.
    - von Riegen, W., ca. 1967-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      46 original drawings, oversized.
    - von Riegen, W., ca. 1967-1977 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      42 original drawings, oversized.
    - Wagner, George, ca. 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      3 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include hunting, psychiatrists.
    - Walkinshaw, Hugh (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Weber, Bob, ca. 1977 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Wenzel, Bill, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      68 original drawings, oversized.
    - Wenzel, Bill, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - White, George H. (Box 10, Folder 45)
      1 original drawing. Subjects include draft-dodging.
    - Whiting, Jim, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Wible, Charles, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      13 original drawings. Subjects include golf, Christmas, boxing, skiing.
    - Wible, Charles, 1973-1979 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      2 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include golf, Christmas, boxing, skiing.
    - Wilson, Roy, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Wirth, Cliff, ca. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      18 original drawings, in addition to the 6 "Funny World" cartoons, includes 12 cartoons titled "L'il Sports" from 1976.
    - Wittry, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Wojahn, Tom, 1970, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Wolfe, George, ca. 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      12 original drawings. Subjects include used books, business.
    - Wolfe, George, ca. 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      16 original drawings, oversized. Subjects include used books, business.
    - Zahn, Bob, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      1 original drawing. From Baldwinsville, NY.
    - The Funny World releases, 1944, 1956-1957 (Box 50, Folder 14-16)
    - The Funny World releases, 1958-1959, 1962, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1-4)
    - The Funny World releases, 1968, 1971-1983 (Box 51, Folder 5-8)
  - Subseries Is. Yogi Bear by Hanna-Barbera
    - Yogi Bear news story, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Yogi Bear dailies, 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Yogi Bear Sunday strips, 1961-1964 (Box 54, Folder 8-11)
    - 1967, 1969-1972 (Box 56, Folder 1-5)
    - 20 original drawings, drawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 32 original drawingsdrawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 43 original drawings,drawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 47 original drawings, drawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 33 original drawings, drawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 32 original drawings, drawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1980 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 3 original drawings, drawn by Gene Hazelton, Sunday strips., 1981 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Yogi Bear daily strips copies, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Yogi Bear Promos, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Yogi Bear bluelines Sunday strips, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Yogi Bear colored Sunday strips, 1976-1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Yogi Bear black and white copies, August-December, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Yogi Bear black and white copies, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Yogi Bear black and white copies, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
    - Yogi Bear coloring diagrams for Sunday strips, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      48 diagrams.
    - Yogi Bear and Flintstones film proofs (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Yogi Bear negatives, 1978-1980 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
    - Yogi Bear negatives, 1978-1980 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries It. Miscellaneous comics
    - Miscellaneous comics proofs, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 20-23)
      Proofs and newsprint copies. Barker Bill by Terry, Dud Dudley by Zekley, Mickey Finn by Leonard, and The Nebbs by Hess.
    - Andrew Tully column, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 10-13)
    - Andrew Tully column, 1975, 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 1-9)
    - Angel Face by Gene, releases, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Ask Jennifer, original art (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Beauty After Forty by Edith Thornton McLeod, releases, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Beaver Crick by Reg Manning, releases, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Big Shot comics proofs, issues 34-35 and others, January, May, September-December (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
    - Blitz Brothers by Sakren, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Bo by Frank Beck, releases, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Bob Hope articles (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Butter and Boop by Black Light Inc., releases, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Carroll Righter Astrology column, 1965-1969, 1974, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 12-19)
    - Chief by Joe Dawley, daily releases, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Children's Tales, 1965-1970 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Children's Tales cancelled, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Children's Tales proofs, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - Cokey by Duane Bryers, releases, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Condominium by Lee Martin, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Dan Flagg by Don Sherwood, releases, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 11-12)
    - Dan Flagg by Don Sherwood, cancelled promos (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Dear Abby by Abigail Van Buren, releases, 1956-1964 (Box 57, Folder 5-13)
    - Dear Abby by Abigail Van Buren, releases, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Dr. Crane releases, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 7-9)
    - Dud Dudley by Zeke Zekley, releases, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - The Face issue 2 proofs (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Football by Terry Brennan (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Frank Kent column, 1951, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 11-12)
    - Hi-ya! by Babe Didrikson (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Hollywood Report by Jack Bradford, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Honey Dear by Devlin, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Hook Slider by Sherry, releases, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Holmes Alexander column, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 10-12)